# **DAYNE GAME**

**FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER** 

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

10 Malibu Key Papamoa Beach, 3118 New Zealand

#### PHONE

02102993594

#### FΜΔΙΙ

daynegame024@gmail.com

#### LINKS

<u>daynegame.me</u>

#### **SKILLS**

HTML & CSS

• • • 0 0

JavaScript & React

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

**REST APIs** 

• • • 0 0

C#

• • 0 0 0

SQL & MySQL

• • 0 0 0

Gatsby

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

Git

• • • 0 0

#### **PROFILE**

A kick-ass 19 year old, that wants that kick-ass job. A talented and ideal candidate for a Junior Developer Position. Small (1.5 years) experience in all stages of web development (Designing, building, testing and deploying). Have built all sorts of small projects to hone my skills.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Line Manager - Class 2, Seeka

Tauranga

Mar 2021 — Present

- · Supervisor/Manager of 12 Staff.
- Used computers to monitor and manage the machines, as well as create reports.

## Web Developer, Bay of Plenty Rugby

Tauranga

Feb 2019 — Jun 2020

- · Lead Web Developer
- · Designed the Website using Adobe XD
- · Built the Front-end using ReactJS and Gatsby
- Built the back-end API using GraphQL and SQL for the Database
  Used NetIfiy CMS for creating, deleting and editing blog posts

Website Link: https://sad-nightingale-b0552e.netlify.app

## EDUCATION

# Bachelor in Applied Information Technology, Toi Ohomai Institute of Technology

Tauranga

Jul 2019 — Jun 2020

# Diploma in Software Development, Toi Ohomai Institute of Technology

Tauranga

Jul 2019 — Jun 2020

## Diploma in Web Development and Deisign, Toi Ohomai Institute of Technology

Tauranga

Jun 2018 — Jun 2019

### REFERENCES

## **Jeff Kranenburg from Toi Ohomai IT Tutor**

027 204 9870